imagetrendelite.com 2018-06-14

# Privacy Policy

## Last updated: July 6, 2017

ImageTrend, Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.imagetrend.com/ and [www.hiretouch.com](http://www.hiretouch.com/) website and other associated ImageTrend Opt-in Marketing activities (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information and other Opt-In Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions or if applicable, your organization’s existing contracts with ImageTrend, Inc.

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name, phone number, postal address, employer name, employer email address, employer phone number, employer postal address, other employer information, or other information ("Personal Information").

We collect this information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your purchase orders, and improving our services and for the following purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not requiring you to enter your personal information more than once
  * To deliver services that you request or purchase
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you
  * To identify advertising and sales campaign opportunities
  * To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from ImageTrend and its partners
  * To fulfill Opt-in marketing activities, like

It is ImageTrend’s practice to easily allow you to remove your name from our distribution list by clicking on a link provided within each electronic communication, or to send an email to support@ImageTrend.com with the subject line “unsubscribe”.

## Log Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie.

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

## Do Not Track Disclosure

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services and/or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

## Other Sites and Business partners

ImageTrend provides links on our site that take you to other websites such as our partner websites and media sites when ImageTrend is covered or featured in the articles. ImageTrend has no control over the content of these other sites, nor the usage of information they gather. We encourage you to review privacy and other policies at third party sites you visit, since those sites are not bound to follow our policies.

## Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

## Compliance With Laws

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 6, 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

## Opt-In Programs

Connectivity Report: ImageTrend will provide your Personal Information, including existing relevant demographic information ImageTrend possesses about you and your employer, and Personal Information from the Connectivity Report web page to ImageTrend’s Interoperability Partners (including Kno2, LLC and other third parties ImageTrend, Inc. may negotiate with for purposes of evaluating or fulfilling information system interoperability). These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks, such as evaluating whether ImageTrend has available Connectivity Partners in your zip code, on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose.

## GENERAL

These are our current internal guidelines, which we make you aware of as a convenience. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to [support@ImageTrend.com](mailto:support@ImageTrend.com). Or you can mail or fax to:

ImageTrend, Inc.  
20855 Kensington Blvd.  
Lakeville, MN 55044  
United States

Fax: +1 (952) 985-5671

## MISSION, VALUES, VISION

Your Vision is Our Passion

Our mission at ImageTrend is to create a better world through technical innovation and a vision of what is possible. We achieve this goal by starting slow, working small and planning long term while visioning big.

We believe ImageTrend succeeds by helping our customers and business partners succeed and attain their goals. The success of any individual employee is tied to the success of the group and the success of the group requires every individual to succeed professionally and personally.

Above all, we believe in our dreams.

## CONNECT WITH US

Follow ImageTrend on Facebook

If you are interested in the development side of ImageTrend, follow us on Facebook at [www.facebook.com/ImageTrend](http://www.facebook.com/imagetrend), at LinkedIn at [linkedin.com/company/imagetrend](http://linkedin.com/company/imagetrend), or on Twitter [@ImageTrendInc](https://www.titter.com/imagetrendinc).

## Follow ImageTrend EDS on Facebook

If you are interested in news about ImageTrend’s Emergency Data Systems division, along with events, tradeshow information, software tips and tricks and more, follow us on Facebook at [www.facebook.com/ImageTrendEDS](http://www.facebook.com/ImageTrendEDS) or on Twitter [@ImageTrendEDS](https://www.twitter.com/imagetrendeds).
